// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which organ system transports oxygen and nutrients to tissues and removes waste products?",
    answer: "A. Circulatory system",
    options: [
      "A. Circulatory system",
      "B. Digestive system",
      "C. Integumentary system",
      "D. Urinary system",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What organ system regulates body functions by chemicals (hormones)?",
    answer: "A. Endocrine system",
    options: [
      "A. Endocrine system",
      "B. Lymphatic system",
      "C. Respiratory system",
      "D. Reproductive system",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What organ system is responsible for removing extra water and waste materials from our body?",
    answer: "D. Urinary system",
    options: [
      "A. Digestive system",
      "B. Endocrine system",
      "C. Reproductive system",
      "D. Urinary system",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which organ system do these organs belong to? Brain, Spinal Cord, Peripheral Nerves",
    answer: "C. Nervous system",
    options: [
      "A. Circulatory system",
      "B. Muscular system",
      "C. Nervous system",
      "D. Reproductive system",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which animal has a ruminant digestive system?",
    answer: "B. Cow",
    options: [
      "A. Chicken",
      "B. Cow",
      "C. Dog",
      "D. Rabbit",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is ABSENT in the avian digestive system?",
    answer: "C. Pancreas",
    options: [
      "A. Crop",
      "B. Esophagus",
      "C. Pancreas",
      "D. Rumen",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the main organ of the circulatory system?",
    answer: "B. Heart",
    options: [
      "A. Blood vessel",
      "B. Heart",
      "C. Nerves",
      "D. Veins",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following parts is NOT suited to the group?",
    answer: "C. Trachea",
    options: [
      "A. Bladder",
      "B. Kidney",
      "C. Trachea",
      "D. Ureter",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is a function of the digestive system?",
    answer: "A. It breaks down our food so that we can absorb (take in) the nutrients.",
    options: [
      "A. It breaks down our food so that we can absorb (take in) the nutrients.",
      "B. It circulates blood to and from the cells of our body.",
      "C. It transports oxygen into the blood.",
      "D. It fights against infections.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following shows one of the pathways of the circulatory system? It circulates blood from theâ€¦",
    answer: "B. Heart into the body and back to the heart.",
    options: [
      "A. Digestive system and move out from the body.",
      "B. Heart into the body and back to the heart.",
      "C. Kidneys to the lungs.",
      "D. Lungs into the body.",
    ],
  },
];
